灯 亮起来
And we have liftoff.
哈罗 欢迎致电未来之家
Yello? House of the future.
菲尔 你有两整天时间可自由支配
Phil, you have two whole days to yourself.
别告诉我你想把全部时间都用来
Please tell me you're not gonna spend them
将家里的装置都连接到ipad上
trying to wire the house to your ipad.
不会 因为我早已完成了
Nope, 'cause I've already done it.
我觉得等你到家的时候
I think when you get home,
你会惊讶地发现我们家
you're gonna be very surprised to see that this house
有个能控制一切的大脑中枢
has an actual functioning brain in it.
真棒 太棒了
Great. Great.
现在出去会会朋友吧
Now go out and see some friends.
我这就出去
I'm headed out now.
我要在殖民健身房进行第三次形体展示
I have a third showing at that colonial.
小卡给了我一张免费入场券去他的健身房
Cam gave me a free pass to his gym.
我 不要太亮[脑子不灵光]
I am--not too bright.
我...
I am--
暗下来[很笨]
Dim!
亲爱的 听听你自己在胡说些什么
Honey, if you could hear yourself.
答应我 你会出去玩玩的
Promise me you'll go outside and play.
我也想你哦
Miss you, too.
菲尔·邓菲 当前时间为2025年
Phil Dunphy, this is the year 2025.
欢迎 你是第一个踏入未来世界的人
Welcome. You're the first one here.
我们先去玩滑水道吧
Shall we hit the waterslide first?
我就待在房里好了
I may just sit in the room for a bit.
拜托 别郁闷了
Ugh! Stop moping!
你不就是没找到舞伴去参加一场傻逼舞会嘛
So you didn't get a date to one stupid dance.
那才不是傻逼舞会
It's not one stupid dance.
那是整个舞蹈季的开场舞
It's the kickoff to the whole dance season.
你是没听到过那些男生们的评价吧
It's like you've never heard boys talk.
嗨 我们是来参加知识竞赛的
Hi. We are here for the academic challenge.
登记名是邓菲
It's under "Dunphy."
或者也可以称为"冠军归来"
or it could be under "Returning champion."
不知道他们会不会为这类东西建档
Not sure how they file these things.
艾丽克斯总是获胜 那很好
Alex wins things, which is great.
但她一直给自己太大的压力
But she puts so much pressure on herself.
我 我都有点希望她今年能输掉
I... I almost wish she would lose this year.
再说 那样我就可以去玩滑水道
Plus, that way, I could go on the waterslide.
那里有螺旋状水道 2秒的自由落体
It's got a corkscrew, 2-second freefall,
在底部还有个雷达枪
And a radar gun at the bottom.
我成了菲尔了
I'm Phil.
不准喝小酒柜里的东西 不准看付费电视
Nothing from the minibar, and no pay-per-view.
我们能不能至少...
Can we at least--
不 你不能把衣服送出去烫
No, you may not send things out for pressing.
宝贝 比赛要1小时后才开始
Honey, we have an hour until the competition.
你想不想去一下参赛者交谊会
Do you want to go to the contestants mixer?
不 我才懒得去教化他们
No, I don't want to humanize them.
你敢相信这是我第一次参加犹太男孩成年礼吗
Can you believe this is my first bar mitzvah?
你会喜欢的 我听说礼物袋里装的都是智能手机
You'll love it. I heard the gift bags have smartphones.
犹太人出手实在太阔绰了
Jewish people are so awesome.
天啊 你看到了吗 她对我回眸一笑
Oh, my god. Did you see that? She smiled at me.
在舞蹈季 那样很正常啦
People get that way in dance season.
从来没有女孩像那样对我笑过
No girl's ever smiled at me like that.
卢克 我们必须参加那个成年礼
Luke, we have to go to that bar mitzvah.
为什么
Why?
我们是有缘人千里相会
There was a connection.
我知道这听起来有些疯狂
I know this sounds crazy,
但我觉得我的人生为这一刻等待了太久
But I feel like my whole life has led to this moment.
你之前也说过类似的话
You made a very similar speech
好说服我妈停下来买西班牙小油条
to get my mom to stop for those churros.
卢克 我需要你的帮助 你比我奸诈
Luke, I need you for this. You're sneakier than I am.
你比我会撒谎 你内心从来不会愧疚不安
You're a bigger liar. You have no moral compass.
听着 谢谢你的诸多"夸奖"
Look, thanks for all the compliments,
但是要闯入一个傻逼派对
But breaking into one stupid party?
那根本毫无挑战
That's not even a challenge.
噢不 有3个成年礼同时举行
Oh, no. Three bar mitzvahs?
这下有点意思了
Now it's interesting.
小卡 停下
Cam, stop.
怎么 我们得让他们离开屋子
What? We have to get them out of there.
怎么磨蹭了这么久
What's taking them?
我们为杰和歌洛莉亚的婴儿房准备了超棒的礼物
We have the most amazing gift for Jay and Gloria's nursery.
都是小卡的主意 是个好大的秋千
It was Cam's idea, and it's a pretty big swing.
才不是秋千呢 绝对不是秋千
It's not a swing. It's not a swing.
我只需要杰和歌洛莉亚离开屋子
I just need Jay and Gloria out of the house
最少大约需要4小时
for a minimum of four hours
好让我的伙计完成安装
So I can have my crew install it.
多"简单"
Simple.
拜托 要是听你的意见
Oh, please. If it were up to you,
我们该送给他们那个礼品登记簿上的东西
we'd get them something off their gift registry.
你是说那个小清单
Oh, you mean the list of things
上面列满了他们明确说想要的东西吗
that they specifically said that they wanted?
他们根本不知道自己想要什么
Oh, they don't know what they want.
再按我就剁掉他的手指
...Before I snap his finger off!
哎呀不
Ay, no.
杰本该取消的 我们不能一起去吃午餐了
Jay was supposed to cancel. We cannot go to lunch.
-噢不 -我很抱歉
- Oh, no. - I am sorry,
他应该去商店把婴儿床买回来的
but he's supposed to pick up the crib at the store,
我太累了 宝宝踢了我一整晚
And I am too tired. The baby kicked me all night.
他要么是个橄榄球队员
It's either going to be a football player
要么是个歌舞团姑娘
or a chorus girl.
可以两者兼具的
You can be both.
我高三的时候 既是右侧中后卫
My senior year, I was a right-side linebacker
也是《金粉世界》音乐剧中的左侧康康舞选手
And a left-side cancan dancer in "Gigi."
她真是抛砖引出你的传奇故事啊 是吧
Wow, she really set you up for that one, didn't she?
是啊 当她说出口的时候
Yeah, when it came out of her mouth,
我当时都快不能呼吸了
I nearly stopped breathing.
你没打电话告诉他们要取消
You didn't call them to cancel.
抱歉 你们要油钱吗
Sorry. You want gas money?
别理他
Don't pay attention to him.
他最近脾气暴得很
He's been very grumpy lately.
好吧 不如这样
Okay, here's a thought--
米奇尔 你和杰一起去婴儿床店
Mitchell, you go to the crib store with Jay.
那样我能与这位美丽的女士
That way I can spend some quality time
-共度美好时光 -不要 我要去躺会儿
- with this pretty lady. - No, I'm going to lay down.
别别别 我要带你们娘俩儿去吃午饭
No, no, I'm gonna take you both to lunch.
好吗 就这么定了 去涂口红 好吗
Okay? There, it's settled. Now go put a lip on. Okay?
好吧 我猜你也不会碍事的
Fine. I guess you won't get in the way.
说真的吗 老爸 这是真心话吗
You mean it, pa? Really and for true?
我不会碍事
I won't get in the way?
带个垫子真明智
Oh, that's a good idea.
是啊 椅子硬邦邦的
Oh, yeah. The chairs are rocks.
查理曼大帝
Charlemagne.
可以花8美元租一天用的坐垫
You can get a 1-day cushion for $8,
或者花12美元租两天用的
or a 2-day for $12.
艾丽克斯·邓菲
Alex Dunphy.
去年我租了两个一天用的 真是大错误
Last year, I got 2 1-dayers--big mistake.
《95条论纲》是谁写的
Who wrote the 95 theses?
我女儿一路过关斩将笑到最后
My daughter went on to win the whole thing,
而我想到的就是
and all I could think was,
我白白多花了4美元啊
"I just flushed $4 down the toilet."
约翰·加尔文[正确答案是路德]
John Calvin.
好样的 艾丽克斯
Whoo! Alex!
我大概是没有想到
I guess I just didn't want to presume
我们会在这里呆两天吧
that we would be here for the two days.
但我要是租一天用的坐垫
But still, what kind of message
那反映了什么心态啊
was I sending with the 1-dayer?
你竟然说好样的
You "Whoo'd" Me?
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
我出局了 我听错问题了
I'm out. I got the question wrong,
那已经够尴尬了 你竟然还说我好样的
which is embarrassing enough without you "Whoo-ing" Me!
艾丽克斯 艾丽克斯 回来 别走
Alex! Alex, come back here. Don't!
想都别想
Don't!
等等 最后四位数是什么再说一遍
Wait, what are the last four numbers again?
对我来说算是个幸运数字了
It's kind of a lucky number for me.
《浑身是劲》就是那年上映的
It's the year "Footloose" came out.
是啊 我真想与你再赛一场
Oh, yeah. And I really am gonna call you for that rematch.
随时随地 我是说 也别太晚
Anytime. I mean, not super late,
但是 等等
But... Wait,
你是斗牛犬队的
you're a bulldog?
是啊 你呢
Yeah. You?
我就知道我喜欢你某一点
I knew there was something about you I liked.
你是说除了我让你赢这点之外吗
Oh, you mean besides me letting you win?
今天有非常重要的一场比赛
You know, we have a big game today.
想要一起看吗
You wanna watch it together?
惨了 我的形体展示快迟到了
Shoot. I'm--I'm late for a showing.
别有压力 如果你喜欢的话
No pressure at all, but if you feel like it,
可以来我家一起看 我短信告诉你地址
we could watch it at my place. I could text you the address.
好的 那谢谢了
All right. Well, thanks.
见到你真高兴 菲尔
Hey, it was great meeting you, Phil.
我也是 戴维
You, too, Dave.
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
你对这家健身房的说法完全正确
Yeah, you were totally right about this gym.
我刚遇到一个超帅的男人
I just met the cutest guy.
我跟你说过什么来着
What did I tell you?
那地方就像个放了哑铃的Gay吧
That place is like a gay bar with dumbbells.
真多余
Redundant.
我还不太了解他
Well, I don't know much about him,
但他邀请我去他家
but he invited me over to his place
一起看橄榄球赛
o watch a football game tonight.
老天啊 约会呀
Oh, my gosh, a date.
我很看好你们哦
I have a good feeling about this.
别这就开始计划婚礼了
Oh, well, don't start planning the wedding yet.
我还不确定这是不是那种情侣约会
I mean, I'm not even sure if it's a date date.
你和他在"约炮中心"相遇
You met him at hook-up central.
当然是那种情侣约会了
Of course it's a date date.
我准备好开始情侣约会了吗
Am I even ready for a date date?
艰难的爱情时期 戴维
Tough love time, David--
西蒙六个月前离开了你
Simon left you six months ago,
你排斥所有人接近你
and you're bumming everyone out.
现在是时候重返情场了
It's time to get back up on that horse.
希望今晚能见到你 戴维
Hope to see you tonight, Dave.
我都记不得上一次某个男人
I can't remember the last time
对我这般狂吼是什么时候了
a man made that sound for me.
她不在这 我们找错了成人礼派对
She's not here. We have the wrong bar mitzvah.
如果你喜欢上等肋排就来对了 "奶奶"
Not if you like prime rib, bubbie.
你说过要装得像一点
You said to blend.
我在拿犹太糕点的时候顺便学了几个短语
I picked up some expressions at the latke station.
对了 其实都是薯饼
P.S.--They're hash browns.
我们不用装着融入了
We're not blending.
她肯定在另外两个成人礼的其中之一上
She's at one of the other two.
快点
Come on.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
那家伙真莽撞
Such a hurry, this one.
快点
Come on.
太可爱了
That is too cute.
那是什么玩意儿
What the hell is that?
那是商店的吉祥物 拥抱兔
Oh, that's the store mascot. That's hugga bunny.
-他到处晃悠 拥抱 -行了 我知道
- He goes around and he hugs-- - No, I get it.
流感季节到处抱"真好"
Nice for flu season.
他应该叫结膜炎兔
He ought to be called conjunctivitis bunny.
好吧
Okay.
这样 爸爸
Uh, so, dad,
婴儿床在那边 但既然我们在这边
The cribs are over there, but while we're here,
给你个小建议 买多少连体衣都不嫌多
a little advice--you can never have too many onesies.
任何场合 任何时间
All right? Any event, day or night.
给宝宝套上一件 再穿上双袜袜
Throw one on, little pair of booties,
就可以出发了
boom--ready to go out.
把它穿在身上 显得很随意
Dress it up, you could dress it down.
也可以...爸爸
You could--dad?
爸
Dad?
我爸明显有什么心事
Something was clearly going on with my dad,
但我可不想瞎搀和
but I wasn't about to get sucked in.
以前也发生过
It's happened before.
"爸 你好像有些难过 能跟我说说吗"
"Dad, you seem sad. Do you wanna talk?"
"说什么 我们什么关系 闺蜜吗"
"Talk?! What are we, girlfriends?"
引用"运动"来解释
To use a sports reference,
把橄榄球收起来吧 露西
put the football away, Lucy.
我都没想踢
I ain't kickin'.
那就周六中午
So Saturday noon?
-周六中午可以 杰 -好的
- Saturday noon's fine, Jay. - Yeah.
爸爸 我给你挑了一个尿片包
Hey, dad, I picked you up a diaper bag.
有趣的设计在于 这个隔热袋
Fun fact-- this insulated pouch
可以让一瓶普洛赛克酒保持冰凉
will keep a bottle of prosecco cold
足以撑过整场儿童乐队表演
for an entire Wiggles concert.
你好
Hi.
-米奇 这位是 -鲍勃·詹森医生
- Uh, Mitch, it's doctor-- - Bob Jensen.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
杰 再见
Jay, I will see you.
好的 到时候见 鲍勃
Yeah, I'll see you then. Good, Bob.
医生 毛背心
Doctor? Sweater vest?
我爸表现的很诡异
My dad acting all shifty?
他在看心理医生
He was seeing a shrink.
"爸爸 我看得出你在为什么事情煎熬"
"Dad, I can see that you're going through something."
"我还能看见你胸罩带呢 奥普拉大妹子
"And I can see your bra strap, Oprah.
管好自己的事儿吧"
Mind your own business."
把那个橄榄球放好 露西
Tee up the football all you want, Lucy.
我仍然没想踢
Still ain't kickin'.
她显然听错了问题
She clearly misheard the question.
这里的音响效果太差了
The acoustics in here are terrible.
尤其对于一个耳朵发炎
Especially for a little girl
-刚刚痊愈的小姑娘而言 -我的天
- just getting over an ear infection. - Oh, my god,
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
-我在为你解释 -我听到了
- I was explaining your-- - Oh, I heard,
因为我耳朵没事
because my ears are fine.
对不起 我没让她这么干
I'm sorry. I didn't ask her to do this.
我是想帮你
I'm trying to help you.
你不是想帮我 是想帮你自己
You were not. You were trying to help you.
你生气是因为现在你不能像牵着小马驹一样
You're just mad because now you can't parade me around
-拉着我到处展览了 -才不是这样的
- like some show pony. - That is not true.
别抵赖了 你买的是2天用的垫子
Oh, don't deny it. You bought the 2-day cushion.
你们有什么资格评判我
Who are you to judge?
谢谢你带来的欢乐的一天 再见
Thank you for a fun day, okay? Good-bye.
-现在就再见吗 -小卡 对不起
- Good-bye? - Ay, cam, sorry,
可是午饭吃了两个小时
But the lunch was two hours,
然后你又让我看你住过的第一间公寓
and then you had to show me your first apartment.
你能相信我以前过着怎样的生活吗
Oh, could you believe how I used to live?
我现在真得补个觉
I really need to take a nap now.
不行不行不行
No. No, no. No. No. No, no. No, no.
你知道吗 我有件事希望你去做
You know what? I have, uh, something I want you to do
可比补觉更让人放松
that's even more relaxing than a nap.
-真的 -不 我就想睡一会儿
- Yeah. - No. I want to take a nap.
我"男人"来了
There's my man.
我来了 你"男人"
That's me. Your man.
我带来了菠菜酱 我也不知道为什么
I brought spinach dip. I don't know why.
我告诉你为什么 因为它好吃
I'll tell you why. 'cause it's delicious,
而且你是个好客人
and you're an awesome guest.
-进来吧 -好啊
- Get in here. - All right.
-你好吗 -还好 你呢
- How are you? - Good. You?
还好 顺便说一下
Good. Uh, by the way,
我给我小舅子和他爱人留了口信
I left a message for my brother-in-law and his partner
让他们也过来
to join us, too.
多一些人 好的
Oh, more people. Good.
-房子不错 -谢谢
- Nice house, by the way. - Thanks.
等一下 那是你的家人吗
Wait a minute. Is that your family?
你结婚了吗
Are you married?
是的 不过别担心 今晚家里都属于我们
Yeah, but don't worry. We have the house to ourselves.
他们都出城去了
They're all out of town.
我已经好久没过"男生之夜"了
I am long overdue for a boys' night.
所以说 你妻子不介意...
Oh, so your wife is okay with--
不介意 还是她提议的
Oh, yeah. She suggested it.
她知道我偶尔需要跟男人们"玩玩"
She knows I need this every so often.
只要我事后"清洗干净" 她没意见的
Long as I clean up afterwards, she's fine.
你想喝一杯玛格丽特酒吗
You ready for a margarita?
好的
Sure.
静气凝神对不对
Soothing, right?
你看 音乐让婴儿放松
You see, as the music relaxes the baby,
你也放松了
you relax.
才没 你让宝宝在我膀胱上跳呢
No, you're making the baby jump on my bladder.
一首关于妓女的歌怎么能让人放松呢
How can it relax listening to a song about a hooker?
她不是妓女 她是一名私人舞蹈家
She's not a hooker, she's a private dancer.
她为钱而舞
A dancer for money.
她会做任何你想让她做的事情...
She'll do what you want her to--
我的天 我教过莉莉这首歌
Oh, my gosh, I taught lily this song.
不好意思
Excuse me.
喂
Hello?
他已经结婚了
He's married.
跟一个女人
To a woman.
她外出了
Yeah, she's out of town.
我不知道 他们估计是达成了
I don't know. They must have
某种协议什么的
some sort of arrangement or something.
那又怎样 若他们彼此心知肚明
So what? If they know about it,
管那么多干嘛
who cares?
反正你也还没准备好认真谈恋爱
You're not ready for a relationship anyway.
玩玩而已嘛
Just have some fun.
感觉好怪 他还邀请了其他人来
It feels weird. He has other people coming over.
我觉得我还是走吧
I think I'm gonna bail on this.
他是在试探你 就像你也在试探他一样
He's just feeling you out like you're feeling him out.
放心吧 其他客人最后一定会神秘爽约
I promise you, these other guests will mysteriously cancel.
稍等一下 亲爱的
Hold on just a second, sweetie.
你好
Hello?
你们还过来吗
Hey, you guys still coming?
我忘了打给你 我们去不了了
Oh, I forgot to call you. We have to cancel.
没关系 再见
No problem. Bye.
我们有更多玛格丽塔酒喝了
More margaritas for us.
其他客人刚刚说不过来了
The other guys just cancelled.
你还在吗
Are you still there?
你说对了 其他客人不来了
You were right. The other guys just cancelled.
瞧吧
See?
听我说
Now listen to me.
你要喝两杯玛格丽塔酒
You're gonna have two margaritas.
也许可以喝第三杯 他讲笑话你就笑
Maybe start a third. Laugh at his jokes.
但笑声不能太尖
But not in that high falsetto thing.
要有点男人的磁性 来练习一下
Something more manly. Let's practice.
我才不要跟你练习笑声
Hey, I'm not gonna laugh for you.
你有时控制欲太强了 你知道吗
You can be very controlling, you know that?
为什么所有人都说我控制欲强
Why does everybody say I'm controlling?
我得挂了
Oh. Gotta go.
看来今晚寒舍只对斗牛犬人开放了
Looks like this kennel is for bulldogs only.
你还好吗
You all right?
没事 我很好
Yeah, I'm all right. I'm great.
那就好
Oh, good.
听着 我不想弄得很古怪
Listen, uh, I-I don't want this to sound weird,
但是
But, um...
但你和我 今晚 这算是...
But you and I, tonight... Is this, uh...
抱歉 戴维 你说什么
Sorry, Dave, what was that?
没什么
Nothing.
给您
Here you go.
只需交一点费用 我们就可以送货上门
For a small fee, we can come to your house
并为您组装
and assemble it for you.
我父亲比较习惯自己动手
Yeah, my dad's more of a do-it-yourself-er,
而且他不喜欢让陌生人进他家
plus he's not one for strangers in his personal space.
好吧 那我帮你搬到车上吧
All right. Uh, well, can I help you carry it to your car?
那样他也不喜欢
Yeah, he's not gonna go for that, either.
那家伙行李箱上有轮子都不用
The guy won't even use the wheels on his suitcase.
他喜欢让别人觉得他是大块头猛男
Likes everyone to think he's this big, tough guy who--
好吧
Okay.
拿出来啦 好 开始干活吧
Yo! There he is. All right. Let's get this done.
爸 其实
Hey, dad, you know--
不 我们不需要别人帮忙 米奇尔
No, we don't need any help, Mitchell.
把你那边举起来
Just pick up your end.
爸 停一下 停一下
Dad, stop, stop, stop.
怎么 刚抬就要休息吗
What? A break already?
爸 你很明显有什么心事
Dad, you're obviously going through something.
你不需要独自承受
Look, you do not have to go through this alone.
我随时愿意倾听你的烦恼
I'm here to talk if you want.
米奇尔 你人真好
That's really nice of you, Mitchell,
但真的要在这里谈吗
But do you wanna do it here?
因为我在那边看到一张小公主桌
'cause I saw a little princess table
上面还有一套茶具
with a tea set on it.
我们父子小闺蜜可以去那好好聊聊
You and I could have a real gab fest.
我真是不长记性
Argh! I'm such a blockhead.
我们能赶紧把这东西搬上车吗
Can't we just get this into the car?
怎么 你怕去看心理医生迟到吗
Why? So you're not late for your shrink session?
-什么 -是啊 我发现了
- What? - Yeah. I picked up on that.
爱抱兔子的老头 那个我也看到了
Bunny hugger! Saw that, too.
转玩具架的老头
Mobile spinner.
老子对天发誓
I swear to god...
你躲在这里做什么
What are you doing back here?!
我没有房间钥匙
I didn't have the room key,
也不想被任何人看到
and I don't want to be seen in public.
我考虑了你刚才说的话
I thought about what you said before...
中国的最后一位君主
When did China's last emperor
-是在哪年登基的 -1909年
- ascend the throne? - 1909.
你说我其它什么都行
And you can say a lot of things about me,
但我不是那种把期望寄托在孩子身上的人
but I am not someone who lives through her kids.
答错了 是1909年
Sorry. It's 1909.
要问我喜不喜欢看到你成功
Do I like to see you succeed?
我肯定喜欢
Of course I do!
-氚是哪个元素的同位素 -氢
- Tritium is an isotope of what element? - Hydrogen.
但要问我是否需要你的成功
But do I need that to
来证明自己的价值
make myself feel important?
那绝对不是
Absolutely not.
错 答案是氢
No, the answer is hydrogen.
说实在的 我真的有点寒心
As a matter of fact, I'm a little hurt
你竟然认为我这么肤浅
you would think I was so shallow.
波斯帝国的斯库德拉辖地包括哪两个区域
The Persian satrapy of Skudra included which two areas?
马其顿和色雷斯
Macedonia and Thrace.
我认识几个当妈的是那样 但我不是
I know moms like that, and that is not me.
绝对不是
No way.
马其顿和色雷斯
Macedonia and Thrace.
开什么玩笑
Are you freaking kidding me?!
马其顿和色雷斯 那是什么玩意
Macedonia and Thrace? What even is that?!
你连听都没听 我们怎么会输的
You're hardly even listening! How could we lose this?!
我居然说了"我们"
I said "We."
是啊 你有时就这样
Yeah. You do that sometimes.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我就是那种妈妈
I am one of those moms.
我很爱你赢的时候
I like it too much when you win.
我好喜欢对其他妈耍威风
I really love lording it over the other moms.
在我们家 你也只能指望拿我炫耀了
Well, in our house, I'm kind of your only source for that.
那还用你说
You're telling me.
海莉只会给我发她涂了指甲油的照片
Haley e-mails me pictures of her nails.
卢克还问我他是不是有猫头鹰基因
And Luke asked me if he's part owl.
他的头是挺能转的
He does get his head pretty far around.
艾丽克斯 真对不起
Alex, I'm so sorry.
没关系啦
It's okay.
可能你是给我施加了点压力
Maybe you do put pressure on me,
但我给自己的压力更大
but it's nothing compared to what I put on myself.
我想我只是想为今天的事找个人来怪罪
I guess I needed somebody to blame for what happened today,
而你恰好撞枪口上了
And there you were.
你知道我很敬畏你的 对吧
You know I'm in awe of you, right?
起来 我知道这地方的后门
Come on. I know a back way out of this place.
等等 这东西你不打算还了吗
Wait. Don't you have to return that?
才不 我可花了不少钱的
No way. I paid good money for this.
-我们带着它去玩滑水道 -好吧
- We're taking it down the waterslide. -Okay.
她居然也不在这里
How can she not be here, either?
-我绝望了 -有点信心
- This is hopeless. - Have a little faith.
埃及人把犹太人逼到红海边上的时候
Did the Jews give up when the Egyptians chased them
他们放弃了吗
to the banks of the red sea?
你是从哪儿知道这些的
How do you know all this stuff?
难道就我一人听了曼纳汉姆叔叔的祝酒词吗
Was I the only one listening to uncle Menachem's toast?
很高兴这对古犹太人管用
Well, I'm glad it worked out for the ancient Jews,
但是眼下
But at the moment
-我可没看见上帝怎么帮我了 -看
- I don't see God doing me any-- - Look!
我不想让你难堪
I'm not gonna embarrass you,
限你一分钟之内离开
but you got one minute to get out of here.
你也是
You, too.
就这样也挺好的
It's for the best.
到处瞎转悠真让我有点劳累了
All this sneaking around was kind of weighing on me.
-我们拿了礼物袋就走吧 -不
- Let's just grab our gift bags and go. - No.
我还有50秒呢
I still have 50 seconds.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你好
Hi.
我叫曼尼·迪尔加多
My name is Manny Delgado,
从你今天在大厅对我微笑后
And I've been searching for you
我就一直在找你
since you smiled at me in the lobby today--
或许我已经寻觅你一辈子了
Maybe even my whole life.
我之前期待能与你一起共度良宵 但现在太晚了
It's too late for us to have the magical night I was hoping for,
但有件事尚不算晚
but it's not too late for us
那就是为错过的良宵留下美好的纪念
to have a memento of what might have been.
我会等你
I'll be waiting.
好了 米奇
Okay, Mitch--
太迟了 不想听
Too late. Not interested.
给我听着
Now listen.
我就不信了 我去开后门
Okay, you know what? I'm just gonna go out the back.
车门和天窗都锁了
Door, sunroof-- all on lockdown.
行了 听着 你今天看见的那个人
Okay, look, that guy you met today--
他是个心理医生
he is a shrink.
但我并不怎么去
But I don't see him all the time.
你妈和我在离婚前去了几次
You mom and I saw him a little before the divorce.
但有时我碰到了点什么事
But every now and then, something comes up for me,
我也会去他那调整一下
and I go in for a tune-up.
如果你是在等我问你 最近怎么了
If you're waiting for me to ask what's going on with you,
那你还是别等了
you just better keep waiting,
因为我不想再自讨没趣
'cause I learned my lesson.
我为某件事心情不怎么好
I'm down about something--
我知道这事迟早要来
something I knew was coming,
现在终于来了
and now it's finally happening.
我的办公室今天就要变成婴儿房了
We're turning my office into the nursery today.
你一副打了败仗般的悲伤抑郁神情
You've been moping around like you lost your platoon
-就为了一个房间 -不止是房间的问题
- over a room? - Not just a room.
整个家里也就在那间房
It's the only place in this house
我能关上门读本书或喝杯酒了
where I can still close the door and read a book or have a drink.
只有那个房间是完全属于我的
Everything in there was mine.
谁在乎 每个人都有烦心事
Ah, who cares? Everybody's got their problems.
不
No.
我这边的门还是能开的
You know, I can still open my door.
你只是把你自己反锁了
You just locked yourself back in.
听着 爸 我...
Look, dad, I...
我之前也为莉莉的卧室放弃了我的家庭办公室
I had to give up my home office for Lily's bedroom,
我对此也很伤心
and I was upset about it, too.
没到要抱兔宝宝的地步 但也...
Wasn't hugging bunnies, but...
行了你
All right.
我 我意识到这不是办公室或房间的问题
I-I realize that it wasn't about an office or a room.
而是莉莉将要带来的全面改变
It was about how Lily was gonna change everything.
但我们一接她到家
But once we got her in there,
我不知道 我 我就 不再想那事了
I don't know. I-I just-- I never looked back.
是啊 我想我可能就是对现状有点紧张
Yeah, I guess I'm just nervous about everything, you know.
-是啊 -谢谢你 孩子
- Yeah. - Thanks, kid.
知道不 我忽然想起来
You know, I'm just recalling
你和克莱尔快要出生的时候
me grumbling about giving up my MG roadster
我要放弃那名爵跑车也很是不爽
when you and Claire came along.
那车超酷 没后座呢
Great car. No backseat.
想起来真是有趣 我们认为最愚蠢的事...
Isn't it funny? The stupid things that we think--
-她是我的小宝贝 -如此重要
- She was my baby. - are so important.
我想算下来 我们总共有50只鸡
I guess all told, we had about 50 chickens.
差不多115头猪
Maybe 115 head of hogs.
大概 55头牛
Let's see, 55 cattle.
哎呀你知道怎么样才好玩吗
Oh, you know what'll be fun?
我想想还记不记得它们的名字 有...
Let's see if I can remember all their names. There was...
艾尔伯特 莉莎
Albert, Lisa
斯特夫和麦克
Steph, and Mike
歌洛莉亚 别走 歌洛莉亚
Gloria! No, Gloria!
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
不 我一个故事都不想再听了
No. I do not want to hear one more story.
我现在要去小睡一会儿
I am going to take a nap now.
好的 当然了 悉听尊便
Okay, yeah, sure. Whatever you want.
今天你说了算
This day's about you.
-只是有一件事 -别再有事了
- Just one more thing-- - No, no one more thing!
我只是想拍张照片
I just wanted to take a picture, you know,
以此纪念我们这么特殊的一天
To commemorate our special day.
好吧 你要照就照吧
Okay, fine! Take the picture!
不 这里不行 光线太差
No, not here. The lighting's terrible.
我想可以在
I was thinking we could take it...
新的婴儿房里拍
in your new nursery!
不 小卡 不
No, Cam. No.
但是 歌洛莉亚 过来...
But, Gloria, come--
必须有人点醒你 你这样不行
Somebody has to tell you this. No.
你想掌控一切 你想掌控别人的生活
You try to control everything. You take over people's lives!
你这个人总是那么过火
It's always too much with you!
也许我们应该在外面走廊上谈这个
You know, maybe we should talk about this out in the hallway.
为什么 因为外面光线更好吗
Why, because there's gonna be better lighting over there?
你又这样 小卡 你又这样
You're doing it again, Cam. You're doing it again!
你说得对 我太过火了
You're right. I am too much.
我是控制狂 我喜欢干预别人
I do control. I do barge.
我会叫我朋友阿伯拉德回来把这个涂掉
I'll have my friend Abelard come back and paint over it.
你把我整天拖在外面就为了这个吗
So this is why you kept me outside all day?
好让你的朋友阿拉伯什么的来画这个礼物
So that your friend Aburar could come and paint a present?
是啊 我怎么不能像正常人一样从你的
Yeah, rather than getting you a gift off your registry
礼物登记簿中选一样呢
like a normal person.
-我好蠢 -我爱死了
- I'm so stupid. - I love it!
真的吗
You do?
那画就和你一样
It's just like you--
丰富多彩 生机勃勃 超级有爱
Full of color... And life... And love.
我真心觉得你会喜欢的
I really did think you'd love it.
什么情况
What's going on up here?
-靠 -那不是我的主意 我告诉过小卡
- What the... - Okay, that was not my idea. I told Cam--
我告诉他这样在人家墙上乱涂太过分了
I told him that's a lot to put on someone's wall.
等下 我喜欢
Hold on. I like it.
-真的吗 -多谢 小卡
- Really? Oh... - Thanks, Cam.
-你真的... -现在放弃这房间容易多了
- You actually-- - Makes it easier to give up the room.
就差那么一点儿[太近了]
Wow, that's close.
那家伙就出界了一点儿
Guy was an inch out of bounds.
暂停[够了]
Time-out.
知道吗
You know what?
不把这事儿"搞定"
I'm not gonna be able to relax
我没法真心乐起来
until I get this out of the way.
洗碗机
Dishwasher.
超酷的吧
Pretty cool, huh?
是啊 的确是
Yeah. It is.
你可以
Hey, do you think...
再帮我倒一杯吗
mind if I freshen this?
没问题 我来吧
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Allow me.
哇 你的手在发抖
Wow. Your hand's shaking.
记住咯 戴维 只是比赛[游戏]而已
Remember, Dave, it's just a game.
我的天 我的天
Oh, god! Oh, my god! my gosh.
-我来擦 -没事的
- Oh, come here. - It's all right.
-有点湿罢了 -不 你都湿透了
- I'm--I'm just a little wet. - Oh, no, you're drenched.
你这样没法坐 不如
You can't sit in that. You know what?
脱掉吧 我扔到烘干机里
Take that off. I'll throw 'em both in the dryer
我去拿两件干净的
and get us a couple of clean ones.
好的
Okay.
我猜反正也总是要脱的
Well, I guess this is something we're doing.
断球
Interception!
-加油 伙计 -加油
- Come on, buddy! - Come on!
加油 伙计 触地得分
Come on! Come on, buddy! Touchdown!
真是太兴奋了
How exciting is this?!
人家都等了好久了
Oh, it's been so long.
-怎么了 -没什么
- What's happening? - Uhh. Nothing.
是我的车钥匙"顶"到你
Oh, my car keys.
见鬼 电视挂了
Shoot. The TV went off.
肯定是什么"搞"坏了
Must have screwed something up.
知道吗 没关系
You know what? It doesn't matter.
楼上还有电视
There's another one upstairs.
不如我们上楼去卧室
How about we head up to the bedroom
来个中场"狂欢"
for some halftime festivities?
那 好吧
Oh... Okay.
我们"上"吧
Let's do this.
我都忘了这样有多开心了
I'd forgotten how much fun this can be.
我们应该定期聚下
We should make this a regular thing.
菲尔 菲尔 等等
Phil, Phil, wait.
我想我还是回家好了
Uh, I think I'd better just head home.
-什么 -我刚结束一段长期恋情
- What? - I'm just coming out of a long-term relationship,
我觉得我现在内心依然脆弱
and I guess I'm still pretty fragile.
不是说我玩得不开心
It's not that I haven't had a-a great time.
没关系 我懂的
Not at all. Hey, I get it.
我也曾经有过肝肠寸断的几晚
I've spent a few nights in heartbreak hotel.
如果有我能帮得上的
If there's anything I can do...
你对我的帮助比你想像的大得多
You've already done more than you know.